Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1985-037
  - Housing Off., Misc. Reports, 1/80-4/1981; PAD 8.18.1 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18.1)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, 5/77-7/1982; PAD 8.18.2 (Box 1, Folder PAD 8.18.2)
  - Buck House, 3/1979-7/1982; PAD 8.18.4 (Box 2, Folder PAD 8.18.4)
  - Escondido Village, 10/1979-7/1982; PAD 8.18.7 (Box 2, Folder PAD 8.18.7)
  - Fraternities/Sororities, 5/80-10/1981; PAD 8.18.8 (Box 2, Folder PAD 8.18.8)
  - Housing for Students, 6/1981-5/1982; PAD 8.18.11 (Box 2, Folder PAD 8.18.11)
  - Registrar, 1/1981-8/1982; PAD 8.21 (Box 2, Folder PAD 8.21)
  - Enrollment Data, 6/80-11/1980; PAD 8.21.1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 8.21.1)
  - Minority Enrollment, 10/80-3/1981; PAD 8.21.2 (Box 2, Folder PAD 8.21.2)
  - Minorities, 6/80-3/1981; PAD 9 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9)
  - Black Affairs, 10/80-5/1982; PAD 9.1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.1)
  - Chicano Affairs, 10/80-7/1982; PAD 9.2 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.2)
  - Chicano Affairs, 1/80-8/1982; PAD 9.2 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.2)
  - MECHA, 2/77-3/1980; PAD 9.2.2 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.2.2)
  - Native American Indian Affairs, 9/1979-8/1982; PAD 9.3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.3)
  - Asian American Affairs, 3/80-2/1981; PAD 9.4 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.4)
  - Women at Stanford, 12/1979-7/1982; PAD 9.5 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.5)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 9/1981-8/1982; PAD 9.6 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.6)
  - Task Force on Women, 8/80-10/1980; PAD 9.6.1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.6.1)
  - Affirmative Action for Women, 10/1979-6/1982; PAD 9.6.3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 9.6.3)
  - Personnel and Employee Relations, 2/1981-6/1982; PAD 10 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10)
  - Employment Inquiries and Requests, 6/78-6/1982; PAD 10.1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.1)
  - Management Self-Study, 4/1981-7/1982; PAD 10.3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.3)
  - Management Self-Study, 9/1981-8/1982; PAD 10.3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.3)
  - Appt. of Lect. and Shrt.-trm. Teachers, 9/80-7/1981; PAD 10.6 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.6)
  - United Stanford Employees, 4/1982-8/1982; PAD 10.7.8 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.7.8)
  - Personnel Policies/Hiring Practices, 1/1981-7/1982; PAD 10.8 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8)
  - Collective Bargaining, 9/1979-4/1981; PAD 10.8.2 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.2)
  - Grievance Procedures: Faculty/Staff, 10/80-1/1982; PAD 10.8.10 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.10)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 7/1979-12/1980; PAD 10.8.3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.3)
  - Faculty/Staff Fringe Benefits, 9/78-8/1982; PAD 10.8.9 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.9)
  - Benefits for Fllws., Vstng. Schlrs., 2/1981-7/1982; PAD 10.8.9/2 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.9/2)
  - Grievance -- Jill Humphries, 4/1981-1/1982; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievance Hearings: Cases, 8/80-8/1982; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievances: Std., Fac., Acd. Matters, 2/72-8/1981; PAD 10.8.10/3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.10/3)
  - Leaves of Absence, Faculty/Staff, 1/1979-12/1981; PAD 10.8.15 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.15)
  - Retirement, 7/1981-8/1982; PAD 10.8.17 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.17)
  - Early Retirement, 10/80-5/1982; PAD 10.8.17/1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.17/1)
  - TIAA/CREF and Prudential, 6/80-6/1982; PAD 10.8.17/3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.17/3)
  - Salaries, 4/80-8/1982; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.19)
  - Policy: Travel, 11/78-1/1982; PAD 10.8.21 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.21)
  - Tuition Benefits Plan, 3/73-7/1982; PAD 10.8.22 (Box 2, Folder PAD 10.8.22)
  - Univ. Services, Misc., 29099; PAD 11 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11)
  - Archives, 11/72-4/1981; PAD 11.1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.1)
  - Food Service, 30072; PAD 11.3 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.3)
  - Hazardous Waste Disposal, 5/1981-8/1981; PAD 11.4.1 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.4.1)
  - Energy: Information/Misc., 5/80-2/1982; PAD 11.4.2 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.4.2)
  - Crime and Crime Prevention, 2/1979-3/1979; PAD 11.6.2/4 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.6.2/4)
  - Office of Public Events, 4/80-6/1982; PAD 11.7 (Box 2, Folder PAD 11.7)
  - Commencement, 4/80-5/1982; PAD 11.7.2 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.7.2)
  - Dedications: Computation Center, 29221; PAD 11.7.4 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.7.4)
  - Founder's Day, 29646; PAD 11.7.6 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.7.6)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 5/1981-7/1982; PAD 11.7.7 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.7.7)
  - A Publications Service/Communication, 7/1979-7/1980; PAD 11.8 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.8)
  - Copyright Policy, 6/1979-3/1981; PAD 11.8.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.8.1)
  - Records, Privacy of, 2/80-12/1980; PAD 11.8.3 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.8.3)
  - Stanford News Service, 29312; PAD 11.8.4 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.8.4)
  - News Service Reports/Releases, 11/1981-1/1982; PAD 11.8.5 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.8.5)
  - Stanford Press, 10/1981-8/1982; PAD 11.8.9 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.8.9)
  - Voluntary Organizations at Stanford, 10/1979-4/1982; PAD 11.9 (Box 3, Folder PAD 11.9)
  - Business and Finance, 9/1981-8/1982; PAD 12.2 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.2)
  - Vice Pres. for Business and Finance, 3/80-3/1981; PAD 12.2/1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.2/1)
  - Treasurer, 1/1982-2/1982; PAD 12.3 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.3)
  - Stanford Investment Management Off., 7/1981-4/1982; PAD 12.3.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.3.1)
  - Auditing, 1/77-12/1979; PAD 12.4 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.4)
  - Budgets, 6/1979-11/1981; PAD 12.5 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Tuition, 9/80-8/1982; PAD 12.5.4 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.5.4)
  - Financial Reports, 11/1979-10/1980; PAD 12.6 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.6)
  - Policy: Investment Responsibilities, 4/78-3/1982; PAD 12.7 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.7)
  - Consulting Policy/Conflict of Interest, 11/78-8/1982; PAD 12.7.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.7.1)
  - Onsurance/Risk Management, 4/1981-5/1982; PAD 12.8 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.8)
  - Health and Safety, 5/1981-5/1982; PAD 12.8.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.8.1)
  - Taxes, Tax Reform, 9/78-5/1980; PAD 12.9 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.9)
  - Vice President for Development, 8/78-12/1979; PAD 12.10 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10)
  - Office of Development, 12/1981-9/1982; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 12/80-4/1982; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 8/80-4/1982; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Stanford Endowment, 12/78-10/1980; PAD 12.10.2 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.2)
  - Fundraising, 11/78-8/1980; PAD 12.10.3 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3)
  - Estates and Wills, 7/78-8/1979; PAD 12.10.3/3 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/3)
  - Stanford Annual Fund (Inner Quad), 1/78-8/1982; PAD 12.10.3/4 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/4)
  - Gift Policies: Gift Summaries, 4/1981-5/1982; PAD 12.10.3/5 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5)
  - Gifts, Permanent, 1/1979-1/1981; PAD 12.10.3/5-1 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-1)
  - Bing, Peter S., M.D., 28338; PAD 12.10.3/5-8 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-8)
  - Carnegie Corp. of New York, 11/78-10/1979; PAD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - Criley, C.A., 6/80-7/1980; PAD 12.10.3/5-12 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-12)
  - Dickenson, FarIeigh S. Jr., 10/78-12/1979; PAD 12.10.3/5-17 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-17)
  - Glenmede Trust Company, 12/78-3/1981; PAD 12.10.3/5-26 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-26)
  - Joseph S. Drown Research Fund, 9/77-10/78; PAD 12.10.3/5-17.5 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-17.5)
  - DuPont de Nemours Company, 9/73-1/1980; PAD 12.10.3/5-19 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-19)
  - Ford Motor Company, 4/75-7/1980; PAD 12.10.3/5-24 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-24)
  - GMC General Gifts, Scholarships, Fellowships, 9/1979-10/1979; PAD 12.10.3/5-25 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-25)
  - Hewlett Packard Company, 4/1979-9/1981; PAD 12.10.3/5-28 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-28)
  - Hewlett, William R., 8/78-11/1981; PAD 12.10.3/5-29 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-29)
  - Morell, George (Black Mtn. Ranch), 29190; PAD 12.10.3/5-34 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-34)
  - Pacific Gas and Electric Fund, 3/74-4/B0; PAD 12.10.3/5-35 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-35)
  - Packard, David, Mr. and Mrs., 4/72-1/1980; PAD 12.10.3/5-38 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-38)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J.E. Wallace Sterling, 29738; PAD 12.10.3/5-43 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-43)
  - Stewart, Arthur C., 28795; PAD 12.10.3/5-44 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-44)
  - Sunset Magazine -- Lane Publishing Co., 12/74-6/1981; PAD 12.10.3/5-45 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-45)
  - Xerox Corporation, 8/78-10/1979; PAD 12.10.3/5-49 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-49)
  - Cecil and Ida Green Gifts, 1/77-4/1982; PAD 12.10.3/5-52 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-52)
  - Charles M. Piggott Gifts, 3/1981-7/1981; PAD 12.10.3/5-53 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-53)
  - Miller, Harold A., 9/1979-6/B2; PAD 12.10.3/5-54 (Box 3, Folder PAD 12.10.3/5-54)
  - Prospective Donors, 4/1981-4/1982; PAD 12.10.3/12 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.3/12)
  - Foundations, Misc., 9/80-3/1982; PAD 12.10.4 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation, 29037; PAD 12.10.4/1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/1)
  - Texas Instruments Foundation, 10.4/3; PAD 12. (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.)
  - Anonymous Funds, Misc., 6/1979-6/1982; PAD 12.10.4/7 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/7)
  - ARCS Foundation, 1/80-3/1981; PAD 12.10.4/10 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/10)
  - Atlantic Richfield Foundation, 10/78-7/1982; PAD 12.10.4/12 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/12)
  - Bank of America Foundation, 12/73-7/1981; PAD 12.10.4/16 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/16)
  - Baxter Foundation, 11/74-9/1981; PAD 12.10.4/17 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/17)
  - James G. Boswell Foundation, 1/80-6/1980; PAD 12.10.4/21 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/21)
  - Fdn. and Crp. Input on the Campaign, 5/80-2/1981; PAD 12.10.4/33-2 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/33-2)
  - Major Gifts Committee, 9/78-3/1982; PAD 12.10.4/33-7 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/33-7)
  - Commonwealth Foundation, 9/78-5/1980; PAD 12.10.4/47 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/47)
  - Commonwealth Matching Funds (Med. Ctr.), 29160; PAD 12.10.4/48 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/48)
  - S.H. Cowell Foundation, 5/1981-3/1982; PAD 12.10.4/50 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/50)
  - Council on Foundations, Inc., 7/1979-8/1979; PAD 12.10.4/51 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/51)
  - Elizabeth Rankin Crossett Fund, 29618; PAD 12.10.4/52 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/52)
  - Danforth Foundation, 11/1979-3/1981; PAD 12.10.4/55 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/55)
  - Arthur Vining Davis Foundation, 1/80-1/1981; PAD 12.10.4/56 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/56)
  - C and H Dreyfus Foundation, 11/78-3/1981; PAD 12.10.4/60 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/60)
  - Exxon Education Foundation, 9/1981-4/1982; PAD 12.10.4/67 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/67)
  - Ford Foundation, 3/1979-4/1982; PAD 12.10.4/71 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/71)
  - General Electric Foundation, 10/1979-5/1980; PAD 12.10.4/78 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/78)
  - Grant Foundation, 10/73-7/1980; PAD 12.10.4/81 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/81)
  - John A. Hartford Foundation, 29403; PAD 12.10.4/85 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/85)
  - Hazen Foundation, 28976; PAD 12.10.4/86 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/86)
  - James Irvine Foundation, 11/78-3/1982; PAD 12.10.4/103 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/103)
  - Henry J. Kaiser Fund, 10/72-8/1982; PAD 12.10.4/110 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/110)
  - W. K. Kellogg Foundation, 4/1981-7/1982; PAD 12.10.4/112 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/112)
  - Kresge Foundation, 11/78-3/1981; PAD 12.10.4/117 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/117)
  - Medical Center Funds, 9/75-2/1979; PAD 12.10.4/137 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/137)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W., 3/1981-6/1982; PAD 12.10.4/139 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/139)
  - T. Mellon Foundation, 11/78-5/1980; PAD 12.10.4/141 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/141)
  - Charles E. Merrill Trust, 2/1981-3/1981; PAD 12.10.4/143 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/143)
  - William Bennett Munro Memorial Fund, 12/62-9/1981; PAD 12.10.4/150 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/150)
  - 1907 Foundation, 9/80-10/1981; PAD 12.10.4/156 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/156)
  - Paul Piggott Fund, 6/75-6/1980; PAD 12.10.4/175 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/175)
  - Thomas and Katherine Pike Fund, 5/80-6/1980; PAD 12.10.4/176 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/176)
  - Proctor and Gamble Fund, 9/75-6/1980; PAD 12.10.4/178 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/178)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 12/78-4/1981; PAD 12.10.4/1B4 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/1B4)
  - Charles H. Revson Foundation, 29373; PAD 12.10.4/182 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/182)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Foundation, 29587; PAD 12.10.4/187 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/187)
  - Sears and Roebuck Foundation, 2/74-1/1981; PAD 12.10.4/199 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/199)
  - Shell Companies Foundation, 4/80-10/1980; PAD 12.10.4/200 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/200)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 5/80-5/1982; PAD 12.10.4/204 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/204)
  - Spencer Foundation, 10/78-5/1982; PAD 12.10.4/211 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/211)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, Inc., 5/78-3/1981; PAD 12.10.4/216 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/216)
  - John Stauffer Charitable Trust, 9/76-6/1982; PAD 12.10.4/220 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/220)
  - The Tinker Foundation, Inc., 12/78-6/1979; PAD 12.10.4/246 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/246)
  - Varian Funds, 28976; PAD 12.10.4/256 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/256)
  - Volkswagenwerk Stiftung, 3/78-11/1979; PAD 12.10.4/260.5 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/260.5)
  - Fairchild Foundation, 8/78-4/1982; PAD 12.10.4/271 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/271)
  - Fireman's Fund American Foundation, 2/78-10/78; PAD 12.10.4/274 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/274)
  - J. C. Penney Foundation, 28856; PAD 12.10.4/278 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/278)
  - Fnd. Fund for Psychiatric Research, 11/80-12/1980; PAD 12.10.4/285 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/285)
  - Research Corporation, 3/78-4/1979; PAD 12.10.4/288 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/288)
  - The Christensen Fund, 9/78-5/1980; PAD 12.10.4/295 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/295)
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 3/1979-10/1980; PAD 12.10.4/297 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/297)
  - Japan Foundation, 12/78-2/1979; PAD 12.10.4/301 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/301)
  - Union Oil Co. of Calif. Foundation, 3/1979-10/1980; PAD 12.10.4/302 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.10.4/302)
  - Patent Administration, 7/1981-3/1982; PAD 12.11 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.11)
  - Planningr Long Range Estimates, 6/1981-10/1981; PAD 12.12 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.12)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/80-8/1982; PAD 12.14 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14)
  - Policy: Use of Land and Facilities, 12/78-2/1981; PAD 12.14.1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.1)
  - Master Facility Plan/Capital Funding, 29646; PAD 12.14.1/1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.1/1)
  - Classrooms, 12/76-12/1981; PAD 12.14.2 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.2)
  - Names for SU Str., Prk., Bldg., and Misc., 5/1979-7/1982; PAD 12.14.5 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.5)
  - Searsville Project, 1/1979-2/1981; PAD 12.14.6 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.6)
  - Buildings, Buildings Space, 6/80-8/1982; PAD 12.14.7 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7)
  - Art Gallery and Museums, 6/1979-3/1982; PAD 12.14.7/1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/1)
  - Art Museum Task Force, 11/1979-1/1980; PAD 12.14.7 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7)
  - Department of Athletics, 8/1979-8/1982; PAD 12.14.7/2 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/2)
  - Facilities Planning/Monthly Proj. Rep., 5/1981-7/1981; PAD 12.14.7/4 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/4)
  - Bookstore, 29526; PAD 12.14.7/5 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/5)
  - Bowman Alumni House, 1/80-11/1980; PAD 12.14.7/6 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/6)
  - Chemistry, 9/73-6/1981; PAD 12.14.7/14 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/14)
  - Behavioral Sci.: Ctr. for Adv. Study, 10/78-7/1981; PAD 12.14.7/16 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/16)
  - Cowell Student Health Center, 9/78-6/1980; PAD 12.14.7/18 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/18)
  - Economics, 5/1979-7/1980; PAD 12.14.7/23 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/23)
  - Stanford Electronics Lab, 12/78-4/1980; PAD 12.14.7/25 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/25)
  - Encina Hall, 1/75-7/1980; PAD 12.14.7/27 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/27)
  - Facilities Planning, 10/1981-5/1982; PAD 12.14.7/29 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/29)
  - Faculty Club, 8/78-5/1982; PAD 12.14.7/30 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/30)
  - Hansen Laboratories, 10/78-2/1980; PAD 12.14.7/34 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/34)
  - SU International Dev. Ed. Ctr., 6/1979-10/1979; PAD 12.14.7/41 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/41)
  - Jasper Ridge, 1/1981-2/1981; PAD 12.14.7/43 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/43)
  - Libraries, 10/73-8/1981; PAD 12.14.7/46 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/46)
  - Medicine, 10/1979-7/1981; PAD 12.14.7/48 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/48)
  - Memorial Auditorium, 29983; PAD 12.14.7/49 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/49)
  - Memorial Church, 5/1979-8/1982; PAD 12.14.7/50 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/50)
  - Parking, 9/76-2/1982; PAD 12.14.7/53 (Box 4, Folder PAD 12.14.7/53)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 8/1979-7/1982; PAD 12.14.7/64 (Box 5, Folder PAD 12.14.7/64)
  - Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1/74-7/1980; PAD 12.14.7/65 (Box 5, Folder PAD 12.14.7/65)
  - Accounting, 2/1979-4/1982; PAD 12.5 (Box 5, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Payroll, 5/80-7/1982; PAD 12.15.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 12.15.1)
  - Planning Office, 3/1981-12/1981; PAD 12.16 (Box 5, Folder PAD 12.16)
  - Peter Coutts, 5/80-8/1982; PAD 13.2 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.2)
  - Industrial Affiliates Program, 9/78-6/1982; PAD 13.8.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.8.1)
  - Visitors, 2/1982-3/1982; PAD 13.10 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10)
  - Conferences, Misc., 30042; PAD 13.10.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.1)
  - Foreign Visitors, 12/1981-5/1982; PAD 13.10.3 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.3)
  - Visiting Committees, Misc., 2/1981-8/1982; PAD 13.10.5 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.5)
  - Computer Science Advisory Committee, 12/1979-7/1982; PAD 13.10.5/1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.5/1)
  - Earth Sciences Advisory Committee, 29983; PAD 13.10.5/2 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.5/2)
  - Law School Board of Visitors, 3/1981-5/1981; PAD 13.10.5/5 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.5/5)
  - Advisory Council of the Sch. of Eng., 5/1979-5/1981; PAD 13.10.5/7 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.5/7)
  - GSB: Advisory Council, 5/1979-9/1980; PAD 13.10.5/8 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.5/8)
  - Visiting Cttee. of SU Libraries, 12/1981-4/1982; PAD 13.10.5/9 (Box 5, Folder PAD 13.10.5/9)
  - Provost's Office, 12/80-11/1981; PAA 1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1)
  - Provost's Senior Staff, 12/80-12/1981; PAA 1.4.2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.4.2)
  - Dean's Council Correspondence, 6/1979-7/1980; PAA 1.5 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.5)
  - Dean's Council Agenda, 10/80-11/1981; PAA 1.5.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.5.1)
  - Academic Information Center, 3/1979-3/1980; PAA 1.6 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.6)
  - Academic Planning Office, 9/78-2/1980; PAA 1.7 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.7)
  - Dean of the Chapel, 3/1979-11/1981; PAA 1.8 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.8)
  - Undergraduate Education, 3/1981-5/1982; PAA 1.12 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.12)
  - Ad Hoc Cttee. on Distrib. Requirements, 1.12; PAA (Box 5, Folder PAA)
  - Tutoring Program, 29129; PAA 1.12.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.12.1)
  - Urban Studies Program, 10/1979-5/1982; PAA 1.12.2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.12.2)
  - Program in Structured Liberal Ed., 1.12.4; PAA (Box 5, Folder PAA)
  - Graduate Division, 4/1981-5/1982; PAA 1.13 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.13)
  - Graduate Students, 12/80-5/1982; PAA 1.13.2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 1.13.2)
  - Faculty Lists/Statistical Reports, 1/80-8/1982; PAA 2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2)
  - Emeriti, 12/80-8/1982; PAA 2.2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.2)
  - Faculty Appointments, 9/80-1/1982; PAA 2.3 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.3)
  - Junior Faculty, 29983; PAA 2.3 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.3)
  - Joint Faculty Appointments, 29465; PAA 2.3.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.3.1)
  - Faculty and Academic Appt. Procedures, 9/1981-8/1982; PAA 2.3.2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.3.2)
  - Faculty Affirmative Action Fund, 2/80-6/1982; PAA 2.3.3 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.3.3)
  - Faculty Annual Reports, 10/1979-12/1981; PAA 2.15 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.15)
  - Policy: Sabbatical Leave, B/78-7/1980; PAA 2.6.7 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.6.7)
  - Policy: Tenure, 3/80-2/1982; PAA 2.6.9 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.6.9)
  - Faculty Development Program, 10/78-9/1981; PAA 2.7 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.7)
  - Volunteer Leadership Conference, 6/1979-7/1979; PAA 2.7.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.7.1)
  - Fellows of the University, 1/1981-6/1982; PAA 2.9 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.9)
  - Research and Teachings Assistants, 10/78-3/1982; PAA 2.11 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.11)
  - Visiting Faculty, 7/1979-7/1982; PAA 2.12 (Box 5, Folder PAA 2.12)
  - SU National Rating and Accreditation, 1/1979-5/1981; PAA 3.4 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.4)
  - Western Culture Requirement, 11/1981-4/1982; PAA 3.5.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.5.1)
  - Continuing Education, 29252; PAA 3.6 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.6)
  - Freshman Advising, 2/1979-8/1982; PAA 3.7 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.7)
  - Pre-med Advising, 5/80-5/1981; PAA 3.7.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.7.1)
  - Course Credit Issues, 30072; PAA 3.8 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.8)
  - Course Evaluation, 10/78-10/1980; PAA 3.8.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.8.1)
  - Curriculum, 8/76-11/1979; PAA 3.9 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.9)
  - Degrees/Honorary Degrees, 11/78-7/1979; PAA 3.10 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.10)
  - Grading/Student Credit, 3/1981-4/1982; PAA 3.13 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.13)
  - Summer Sessions, 3/1979-4/1982; PAA 3.16 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.16)
  - Post-Doctoral Education, 5/1979-6/1981; PAA 3.17.2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.17.2)
  - Undergraduate Specials, 10/78-7/1982; PAA 3.18.3 (Box 5, Folder PAA 3.18.3)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 5/80-8/1982; PAA 4.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1)
  - HandS: Special and Honors Programs, 10/78-7/1982; PAA 4.1.1 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1.1)
  - Humanities Center, 10/80-5/1982; PAA 4.1.1/2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1.1/2)
  - Interdepartmental Majors, 4/75-12/B0; PAA 4.1.2 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1.2)
  - Afro-American Studies, 5/80-11/1981; PAA 4.1.4 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1.4)
  - Anthropology, 12/74-10/1981; PAA 4.1.5 (Box 5, Folder PAA 4.1.5)
  - Applied Mathematics and Statistics, 3/75-6/1982; PAA 4.1.6 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.6)
  - Applied Physics, 9/78-5/1982; PAA 4.1.8 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.8)
  - Art and Architecture, 11/80-1/1982; PAA 4.1.9 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.9)
  - Sullivan Christensen Fund, 11/77-6/1982; PAA 4.1.9 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.9)
  - Rodin Collection/Cantor Gift, 10/1981-7/1982; PAA 4.1.9/1 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.9/1)
  - Asian Languages, 3/75-3/1982; PAA 4.1.10 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.10)
  - Linguistics, 11/80-8/1982; PAA 4.1.11 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.11)
  - Biological Sciences, 8/1979-4/1982; PAA 4.1.12 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.12)
  - Chemistry, 2/1979-6/1982; PAA 4.1.13 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.13)
  - Classics, 10/1979-7/1982; PAA 4.1.14 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.14)
  - Communications, 9/80-7/1982; PAA 4.1.15 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.15)
  - Computer Science/COSERS, 9/1979-6/1980; PAA 4.1.17/1 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.17/1)
  - Drama, 11/78-6/1982; PAA 4.1.18 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.18)
  - East Asian Studies, 8/78-9/1981; PAA 4.1.19 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.19)
  - Economics, 9/80-8/1982; PAA 4.1.20 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.20)
  - English, 1/1979-5/1982; PAA 4.1.21 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.21)
  - French and Italian, 10/80-7/1982; PAA 4.1.22 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.22)
  - Rene Girard, 1/80-12/1980; PAA 4.1.22 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.22)
  - German, 10/80-3/1982; PAA 4.1.24 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.24)
  - History, 10/1979-7/1982; PAA 4.1.25 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.25)
  - Human Biology, 11/1981-8/1982; PAA 4.1.26 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.26)
  - Mathematics, 9/80-8/1982; PAA 4.1.27 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.27)
  - Hopkins Marine Biology Center, 9/80-2/1982; PAA 4.1.28 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.28)
  - Music, 10/78-6/1982; PAA 4.1.29 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.29)
  - Dept. of Athletics, Phys. Ed. and Rec., 10/1981-8/1982; PAA 4.1.30 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.30)
  - Football Games, 29099; PAA 4.1.30/1 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.30/1)
  - Philosophy, 2/1979-8/1982; PAA 4.1.21 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.21)
  - Physics Visiting Committee, 6/63-8/1982; PAA 4.1.33 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.33)
  - Physics, 10/80-6/1982; PAA 4.1.33 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.33)
  - Astronomy, 10/78-2/1982; PAA 4.1.33/1 (Box 6, Folder PAA 4.1.33/1)